<Document>
	<!-- Q3 - Starting Quadrant -->
	<!-- Warning player of enemies -->
	<Nie>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Nie Siyu">
				Dangerous thing you're carrying there. Careful with the tin heads.
			</Line>
			<Line id="1" owner="Nie Siyu">
				They usually don't bother people unless they're causing trouble.
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</Nie>
	<!-- Shop related dialogue -->
	<Shen>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Shen Xiaodan">
				Rumour is that the owner of these stores has some sort of deal with the City, and with that comes stuff you can't get anywhere else. 
			</Line>
			<Line id="1" owner="Yin">
				(Then maybe I can find something useful in there. I don't have access to the usual gear, so I'll just have to make do.)
			</Line> 
		</Dialogue>
	</Shen>
	<!-- Expository Dialogue -->
	<Joe>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Joe Qi">
				So... Just what the hell happened here?
			</Line>
			<Line id="1" owner="Gau Minzhe">
				Dai Lanfen was killed last night. Gruesome stuff. Cops took her body a while ago. At least I think they were cops, I didn't recognize the uniform.
			</Line>
			<Line id="2" owner="Yin">
				(Dai Lanfen... I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.)
			</Line>
			<Line id="3" owner="Yin">
				(The only thing I can promise you is that I won't give up until I make them pay for what they've done.)
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</Joe>
	<!-- Other -->
	<Kwong>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Kwong Jiang">
				Why exactly is there a shack in the middle of the street?
			</Line>
			<Line id="1" owner="Jow Tengfei">
				Story is that the old man that lives here was so stubborn he refused to sell the land, so they just had to build around it.
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</Kwong>
	<OldManLau>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Old Man Lau">
				What do you want? Another suit trying to kick me out of my home? I've been living here since before you were born. Now git!
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</OldManLau>
	<Chuang>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Chuang Yongzheng">
				Have you spoken with Zhou already?
			</Line>
			<Line id="1" owner="Yi Yaochuan">
				I've tried to, but the guy doesn't budge. Got a stick so far up his ass he can't even wear a hat.
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</Chuang>
	<Lim>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Lim Jianguo">
				What are you looking at? Keep moving.
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</Lim>
	<Sun>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Sun Yingjie">
				Keep moving. I'm not your friend, buddy.
			</Line>
			<Line id="1" owner="Yin">
				And I'm not buddy, pal.
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</Sun>
	<Peng>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Peng Yuet">
				Did you hear about Shiau Heng?
			</Line>
			<Line id="1" owner="Diao Xiaoqing">
				Qiao Huifang must be heartbroken... To leave like that, in the middle of the night.
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</Peng>
	<Feng>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Feng Siyu">
				It's already been almost 30 years since the quake, but the capital never really recovered.
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</Feng>
	<GateInteraction1>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Yin">
				(No matter how many times I see them, the Gates are never not massive.)
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</GateInteraction1>
	<GateInteraction2>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Yin">
				(No good. Even if it could open, going through here would be a bad idea.)
			</Line>
			<Line id="1" owner="Yin">
				(If I recall, there was a flaw in one of the old gates. I should try there.)
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</GateInteraction2>
	<OldGateInteraction>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Yin">
				(There we go, a way into the Old City.)
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</OldGateInteraction>
	<!-- Quadrant 2 -->
	<!-- Expository Dialogue -->
	<Yan>
		<Dialogue id="0">
			<Line id="0" owner="Hou Liwei">
				You know, I go through here everyday, but never quite managed to figure out what this thing is.
			</Line>
			<Line id="1" owner="Yan Renshu">
				It's an old water filter. They started building the Red City from the outside going in, and used this to provide workers with clean water.
			</Line>
			<Line id="2" owner="Yan Renshu">
				They just left this here because it would be cheaper than dismantling it and just fell in disuse.
			</Line>
		</Dialogue>
	</Yan>
</Document>